Embark on an epic journey of family, courage, and coming home.
The Elephant Queen is a documentary, family film directed by Mark Deeble.
Embark on an epic journey of family, courage, and coming
home in this feature-length documentary.
Join Athena, the majestic matriarch, as she leads her elephant herd across an
unforgiving African landscape filled with vibrant wildlife.
Self - Narrator (voice), played by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
The Elephant Queen is a 2018 documentary film directed by Victoria
Stone and Mark Deeble, and narrated by Chiwetel Ejiofor.
It tells the journey of a family of elephants in the African
savannah when they are forced to leave their waterhole.
The film was produced by Lucinda Englehart under the banner of Deeble & Stone.
At the 2019 Critics' Choice Movie Awards, The Elephant Queen was nominated
for Best Science/Nature Documentary and Best Narration.
The film explores themes of elephant, parent child relationship,
family relationships, herd, nature documentary.
The tone is emotional.